{
    "id": "084e3d7395e94740bada8eb85446ac74",
    "title": "English Vocabulary Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "The ship …………………….. during the hurricane.",
            "description": "Founder means sink or go under.",
            "answers": [
                "founded",
                "floundered",
                "foundered"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "58f6d2c7d8744fdebb9562f5cec79ea1"
        },
        {
            "question": "Most of her arguments were ………………………. on facts.",
            "description": "Founded means based or rested. It is the past tense of found.",
            "answers": [
                "found",
                "founded",
                "foundered"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "59d50f89342e428788b3ca6eb990a73b"
        },
        {
            "question": "The explorers have ………………………… something amazing.",
            "description": "Found is the past tense form of find. ",
            "answers": [
                "found",
                "founded",
                "foundered"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "5208d0505d1d491588fb9f87d3b07bc2"
        },
        {
            "question": "It was a neighborhood accustomed to …………………… crimes.",
            "description": "Foul means disgusting. A fowl is a chicken or a related bird.",
            "answers": [
                "foul",
                "fowl",
                "fuel"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "439c01560b7a4db6b9fb99aa3102e5fe"
        },
        {
            "question": "The expedition was ……………………… with danger.",
            "description": "Fraught means filled or loaded.",
            "answers": [
                "fright",
                "fraught",
                "frought"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "fcccddd083cb45d3ac848a9cd139b83b"
        },
        {
            "question": "He was charged with ………………………… for selling deeds to nonexistent land.",
            "description": "Fraud means trickery or cheating.",
            "answers": [
                "frode",
                "fraud",
                "fraught"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "6e16ce364f854532a97410a8393351de"
        },
        {
            "question": "Several vice presidents were involved in the …………………………",
            "description": "Fray means quarrel or fight.",
            "answers": [
                "flay",
                "fray"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "73712642f720477db502359543a56be6"
        },
        {
            "question": "The headmaster ………………………… the boys for their irresponsible behaviour.",
            "description": "To flay is to censure harshly.",
            "answers": [
                "fried",
                "frayed",
                "flayed"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "3f4847343b7b48aba9eaf249bca215dd"
        },
        {
            "question": "Although she is rich she does not like to ……………………….. it.",
            "description": "To flaunt is to show off something.",
            "answers": [
                "flout",
                "flaunt"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "e47e82df9d134dbbb7bf31052e5930bc"
        },
        {
            "question": "Those who ……………………….. the rules shall be dismissed.",
            "description": "To flout is to show contempt for something.",
            "answers": [
                "flout",
                "flute",
                "flaunt"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "4b2bbbe7c16e4c28988386a27bb0de19"
        },
        {
            "question": "Lack of civilian clothes was the one ……………………….. in our escape plan.",
            "description": "Flaw means defect or imperfection.",
            "answers": [
                "flay",
                "flaw",
                "flow"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "6355a3f7a09248eea860b4a95925e630"
        },
        {
            "question": "We caught only a ……………………….. glimpse of the Presidential motorcade.",
            "description": "Fleeting means swiftly passing.",
            "answers": [
                "fleeing",
                "fleeting"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "3bef35f0f9d0431d850fdf3febb37dc7"
        }
    ]
}